This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Initial
Raise up your hands 高く [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
高举你的双手 [所有人都知道我无法停下]
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
掴め Brand new tomorrow [You don't stop]
把握住 崭新的明天 [不会停下]
(You don't stop)
風の中で 自分を知る ずっと最高のDreamだろう
迎风而立 看清自己 正是一直以来最大的梦想
It's a beautiful eternal dream...
...where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
让我们出发 让我们出发
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh raise up you can't stop
哦 无人能阻止我们的崛起
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive go for the highest stake in the gamble.
生きてるだけで何やろうかな
行尸走肉地活着能成什么事
Gamble on 迫る鼓動にテンバリ
赌一把 心跳快得叫人紧张
同じMission 同じ一生
同样的理想 同样地拼命
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
どんだけ夢熱いかが勝負だろ
现在就来比比看谁的梦想更为炽热吧
You can never use the escalator.
Escalator 無しの永遠
没有电梯直达的不朽荣耀
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
足腰鍛え Let's begin yeah
让我们对锻炼身体说yeah
You must eventually climb the stairs.
どうせのぼる階段
反正早晚要爬上的阶梯
心こっちにCustomizeしちゃえばいい
先在这里锤炼自己的内心好了
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
削られて 過ぎる毎日[But you know]
日渐颓废的每一天 [但你知道]
Intense days go by. (But you know?)
攻めがいのあるGameと 笑い飛ばして
对值得攻下的关卡 也能一笑置之
Just laugh it off, 'cause it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it
让我们瞧瞧你的神速
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands ずっと [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
不要放下你举起的手 [所有人都知道我无法停下]
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
走れ Sleepless challenger [You don't stop]
飞驰吧 无眠的挑战者 [不会停下]
(You don't stop)
今に生きる 理由を探す
寻找活在当下的理由
It's a quest of the never-ending dream...
...where you now search for the reason to live.
夢尽きないQuest
梦想无极限的征途
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
让我们出发 让我们出发
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
哦 无人能阻止我们的崛起
来たぞォ
Here they come !
なんなの どうしてそんなにもりあがるの
Why ? What made them so excited ?
どう見る 真子
What's your take, Mako ?
何とも言えないけど
Hard to say, but at the least
the NSX's traction is impressive.
やっぱりドラクションすごいね NSX
このコーナー出口 かなりの急勾配だけど
The exit of this corner is really steep, but it
accelerated quickly without losing balance.
グラつきもしないで猛然と加速していた
FDやっぱ苦しい ワンテンポ遅れる
The FD is at a disadvantage after all,
because its response was one step behind.
北条さんの赤いクルマ 楽しそうなんかじゃない
Hojo's red car wasn't having fun.
でも 黄色いクルマは 笑ってた
But the yellow car was smiling.
相手がNSXであることは
But I knew early on that our
opponent would be using an NSX.
早い段階でキャチしてたし
オレも啓介も何の準備もせずに
It's not like Keisuke and I just
sat back and waited for today.
今日をむかえたわけじゃない
こっちにも切り札はある
We have our own trump card.
展望台のヘアビンを通過
They passed the hairpin at the observatory, and have entered section 4.
第4セクションに入ります
ここからやな
From there...
はじまったか
It's begun.
こっからはもうタイヤいたわれねえけど
I can't conserve the tires from here on, but I'm counting on you, my FD.
たのむぜFD ふんばってくれよ
Please hold on.
あァ もう どうなってんでしょうねバトルの展開
It's so frustrating !
How is the battle going ?!
落ち着け 樹
Calm down, Itsuki.
だって 気になってじっとしていられないですよ
But I'm so worried
that I can't stand still !
現段階では現状維持ってところだろ
They're probably maintaining
their positions at the moment.
NSXが逃げて FDが追って展開が
The NSX tries to flee while
the FD tries to catch it.
Right.
でもよ 本当に勝ってんのかな FD
But do you really think the FD can win ?
何でんすか 健二先輩
What're you saying, Kenji ?
だってさっきの見ただろ
You saw it, didn't you ?
相手は桁違いの速さだぜ
That speed was incomparable.
Besides, it's in the lead position.
しかも先行だ
勝ちますよ絶対
Takahashi Keisuke will win no matter what
because he's Project D's ace in the hill climb !
高橋啓介はプロジェクトDヒルクライムのエースなんですから
拓海だって
Same for Takumi...
第4セクションに入った
They're in section 4.
ここまでは予定通り
Everything has gone as planned so far.
ここからが本物の勝負や
The real battle begins now.
Battle Beyond Expectations
松本 今だから言うけどさ
Matsumoto, I couldn't tell you this until now...
プロジェクトDのドライバーに 啓介を抜擢したことには 迷いがあったんだ
...but I hesitated to pick Keisuke
as a driver for Project D.
藤原の才能のキラメキに比べて
There was a time when he looked inferior, when
compared to Fujiwara with his splendid talent.
あいつはいくらか見劣りしてしもう時期があった
啓介本人もそれはうすうす自覚していたことだろう
Keisuke must have felt it,
more or less, as well.
ドライバー同士なら イヤでもわかる
Drivers naturally figure those things out.
少なからずあせりも感じていたはずだ
He must have felt a certain degree of pressure.
オレとしても
As for me, I didn't want to
favor my blood-related brother.
血のつながった弟だけに
どこかで贔屓目がはいることはさけたかった
だからこそ
That's why I've been trying to distance myself from him, and acted harshly.
つきはなしてきつく接してきたんだ
そうでしたね
Yes, you have.
オレが印象に残っているのは
I remember when Keisuke damaged his car's suspension after going through some oil during our Saitama expeditionary race.
啓介さんが埼玉遠征の時
路面のオイルをふんで サスペンションをいためにことがありましたよね
注:土坂赛前练习时路面被对手浇了柏油 导致启介轮胎打滑
ちくしょう
Dammit !
しんそこ頭にきたぜ
This pisses me off !
ガードレールにあたりちらしているヒマはないぜ
You have no time to vent
your frustration on the guardrail.
FDが壊れたのは
It's your fault that your FD was damaged.
おまえ自身のせいだ
え？オレの
My fault ?
そうだ
Yes. I wouldn't have damaged
my car because of a trap like this.
少なくともオレなら
この程度の罠でクルマを壊すことはしない
Your overconfidence and
carelessness brought you to this.
慢心と油断が原因だ
頭を冷やしてよく考えてみろ
Calm down and think.
あの時
You blamed Keisuke for his carelessness, instead of our opponent's dirty trick.
敵のきたないやり方を非難する前に
啓介さんの油断を責めてましたよね
ちょっとかわいそうなくらいでしたよ
I felt sorry for him.
あいつは昔から 打たれ強いタイプなんだ
He's been pretty tough since he was little.
ほめるよりもへこませるくらいの方が伸びるんだよ
He improves more from getting
chewed out than from receiving praise.
It was around that time when the
look in his eyes began to change.
あのころからかな
啓介の目の色が変わってきたのは
オレが啓介にやらせている タイムを指定する走りこみは
Regarding the training of having Keisuke match a preset time, I was obsessed with the same training a long time ago.
オレ自身が昔 夢中になってやっていたトレーニングなんだ
やみくもに全力で走っても
Surprisingly, you don't learn much when you're desperate and trying to drive fast.
意外と身につくものは少ない
集中力は続かないし
Your concentration doesn't last,
and you'll only put stress your car.
クルマに負担がかかるだけで
コントロールする練習の方が はるかに多くのことを考えるし
But you think hard and discover
more by practicing car control.
多くの発見があるものなんだ
コントロールを極めてこそ
You can reach your limit only
after you perfect such control.
本当の限界に近づける
区間タイムも出ました
I've got the section time.
豪さんにとって
It's nearly Gou's best time.
ほぼトップスピードに近いペースでしょう
このペースについていけるクルマは サイドワインダーにはいない
None of the Sidewinder team
members could keep up with this pace.
さすがは高橋啓介と言えますね
Takahashi Keisuke is the real thing.
今夜も大勢のギャラリーが出てるけど
There are a lot of spectators, but not very
many of them truly understand what's going on.
事の本質を理解できてる奴は ほとんどおらんやろ
一見 均衡しているかに見える今
At a glance, the situation
appears to be deadlocked...
二人のドライバーが どれほど高度なタイヤマネージメントを駆使しているのか
...but both drivers are managing
their tires extremely well.
とほうもなくハイレベルな 玄人好みの攻防っちゅうのは 地味なもんや
A high-level race that appeals to
the experts tends to look uneventful.
そのいい例が藤原だろう
Fujiwara is a typical example.
He's a master of vehicle control.
あれはコントロールの達人だからな
たしかにそうですね
You're right.
藤原に対するライバル意識が
You could say that Keisuke's sense
of rivalry with Fujiwara improved him.
啓介を育てたとも言える
どなん豪雨でも
Whether it's heavy rain or fog, even when he was sick, he never skipped his driving training on Akagi roads.
キリが出ても
カゼをひいていても
藤原则是风雨无阻的秋名山
あいつは赤城道路の走りこみを欠かさないんだ
継続する情熱こそが天才だと
Some say a never-ending passion
is what brilliance is all about...
誰かが言っていたけど
そういうものが啓介にはある
...and Keisuke has something like that.
いい関係ですよね
Fujiwara and Keisuke are
mutually beneficial to one another.
藤原と啓介さんは
実はな 松本
To be honest, Matsumoto, this past month...
この1ヵ月ほど
いや 厳密に言うと半月くらいかな
Actually, in the past
two weeks to be precise...
啓介がぢょっと信じられない領域に入っているんだ
...Keisuke has reached an incredible level.
信じられない領域
An incredible level ?
指定したタイムに 誤差が出ないんだ
His time is dead accurate to the preset time.
ペースが乱されそうな外的な要因が加わっても
Even when he faces obstacles that might
disrupt his pace, he matches the time in the end.
全体で帳尻をあわせてくる
体の中にしっかりとした時計の感覚ができあがっているんだろう
He must have developed
an accurate internal clock.
オレがピークだったころでも
My past peak performance
wouldn't beat today's Keisuke.
今の啓介にはかなわないよ
自分でも同じトレーニグをしてきただけに
I did the same training, so I can
understand how impressive he is.
すごさがわかる
あの長い赤城道路で
It's godlike to drive such a long Akagi road
within an error margin of less than 1 second.
1秒以内の誤差にすべてタイムをそろえてしまうなんて
ほとんど神がかりだぜ
いろんな要素が重なりあって
Many factors have contributed
to Keisuke's breakthrough.
啓介の中で何かが今ブレイクしている
オレが考案したトレーニングが
My training method created
an incredible street racer.
すごいポテンシャルの走り屋を養成してしまった
あいつは今 すさまじく乗れている
His condition is extremely good.
こんなうれしい誤算はない
What a pleasant surprise.
最終戦にまにあった
We made it time for the final battle.
とっておきの切り札は 啓介そのものだ
Our trump card is Keisuke himself.
线位贴得太神了 果然是主场车
小柏 どう見る NSXの走り
Kogashiwa, what's your impression
of the NSX's performance ?
オレには シャカリキにとばしてるようにしか見えませんがね
To me, it only looks like it's
desperately trying to go fast.
アクセルもふんでるし
It's going flat-out, and
the tires are at their limit.
タイヤだってめいっぱいです
何よりクルマの挙動とラインが本気ですよ
More than anything, the lines
show the driver's seriousness.
同感だな
I agree.
それならなぜだ
Then why is Takahashi
Keisuke's FD right behind it ?
高橋啓介のFDがくいついたままなのは
何が起こっている
What's going on ?
なんだか話がちがうんじゃねえか
This isn't what we discussed.
Your car should have
a 15 second advantage.
15秒のアドバンテージを作りました 不満ですかな 15秒では
Do you have any qualms with
only a 15 second advantage ?
十分だ オレを誰だと思うっている 久保さん
It's enough.
Who do you think I am, Kubo ?
Do you think I'll lose to some punk
from Gunma in driving technique ?
群馬から来たヤンキーあがりに
ドライビングで負けると思うか
スッキリしねえぜ
This is really frustrating.
クソ
Dammit, this sucks.
面白くもねえ
なんて 細くて長くてきれいな脚だろ
Slim, long and beautiful legs...
しかもすごくいいニオイする
And she gives off a nice scent.
真子さんて大人の女ヒトだなァ
Mako is a mature woman.
まさかここまでもつれてくるとは
Who would've anticipated a deadlock like this ?
かなり予想外だが
This is really unexpected,
but things are getting interesting.
これは面白くなってきやがったな
北条豪が勝負を決めにいって失敗している
Hojo Gou trying to settle
the match, but he's failing.
やらかしてくれるな プロジェクトD
Project D is quite something indeed.
このヘアピンをすぎれば
There's not much left
after this hairpin curve.
コースは残り少ないし
This must be a surprising
turn of events for Sidewinder.
サイドワインダーにとって これはあきらかに異変でしょう
はじめから2本目3本目を視野にいれていたとは考えにくい
I don't think they've prepared
for a second or third run.
久保英次の立てた作戦にミスがあったということだろ
That means Kubo Eiji made
a mistake in building his strategy.
水面下で何かが起こっているんだ
Something else has happened behind the scenes.
何かが
Something else...
なんやて そんなはずあるかいな
What did you say ?
That's ridiculous !
Do you have the section time ?
区間タイムは出てるか
Yes.
はい
これは
That's...
ありえへん あのFD
...impossible.
That FD isn't built to
match such a high pace.
これほどのペースに対応できるクルマではないはず
どこかに計算の狂いがあったか
Was there a miscalculation ?
いや そんなはずはない
No, that can't be the case.
FD3Sにそこまでのポテンシャルがあるはずがない
The FD3S shouldn't have that kind of potential.
クソ
Dammit !
おい いったいどうなってんだ
Hey, what's happening ?
全開スピードに突入した時にオレは乗れていた
I was on a roll when I went flat-out.
矛盾なく
I know I was.
それなのに何ってそこにいる
So why are you still there ?
何ってはなれない
Why are you putting pressure on me,
instead of falling behind ?
追いつかてくる
神奈川エリア初戦から
Sidewinder tried to dominate us in intelligence gathering by dispatching scout teams since our first race in Kanagawa.
データの収集部隊を編成し
情報戦で圧倒しようと企てだ サイドワインダー
その優秀な参謀である久保が組み立てた作戦が
Seasoned strategist Kubo's plan
didn't work, probably because...
機能しなかったのはなぜか
それはおそらく
...Keisuke's skills, that are refined by his peculiar daily training, greatly exceeded Kubo's expectations.
啓介が日頃から徹底している 独特の走り込みによって培ったものが
久保の想定する範疇を 大きく超えていただからだ
あいつが特訓で培った感覚は
The type of driving sense he's acquired becomes useful in many ways.
いろんなことに応用がきくんだ
Even if you don't control
your car at full throttle...
全開で走らずにコントロールしていても
...you can understand how the car
will behave at its max acceleration.
全開で走った時の挙動がわかるようになってくる
神奈川に入るころから
Around the time when we began our Kanagawa races, Keisuke stopped practicing a flat-out run.
啓介は全開のプラクティスをほとんどしなくなった
その方が多くの情報をキャッチできるし
You can lean more that way.
何より作業の効率が上がって クルマの仕上がりもはやい
And more than anything, you can finish your
car's settings because of improved efficiency.
なるほど そういうことか
I see. That makes sense.
相手にはデータ分析に長けた人間がいることだし
Our opponent has a data analysis expert who can see through any imperfect camouflage.
生半可なカムフラージュをしても見抜かれてしまう
攻めるところは攻めて
By focusing on the critical attacking areas, and going easy on the rest...
その他は流して
うまくペースのデコボコをならしてフラットにしてしまえば
...we created an evened-out pace, which should have
made it difficult for our opponent to gauge our potential.
敵もこちらの本当の戦闘力に迫ることはむずかしいだろう
おまけに今の啓介は流していても
On top of that, Keisuke drives extremely fast even when he takes it easy.
おそろしく速い
さすがの久保も そんなことができるドライバーが公道で育つとは
Even Kubo couldn't anticipate a driver, who's
trained on public roads, could pull such a stunt.
よもや考えないさ
想像を絶しますね
It's beyond my imagination.
They may have figured out
how we control our cars...
ある程度コントロールしていることは気づかれても
限界ゾーンでの情報はほとんど敵には与えていない
...but we didn't give them any information
about our peak performance.
情報戦は五分と五分
This battle of intelligence is even.
すごいな 啓介さん
Keisuke is amazing.
そうか 分かった
Okay, I got it.
ヒルクライムの1本目が終了したぞ
The first hill-climb is over, and the
result is not what we expected.
意外な結果だぜ
逃げきれなかったんだろ
He failed to outrun him, which means the
game is carried over to the second run, right ?
つまり2本目に突入ということだ
Yeah.
それでいい 今ごろあいつの頭の中は
That's the way it should be.
I bet his brain is
frozen like a glacier.
思考が停止して まっしろになってるだろう
たてなおすための時間はある
But he has time to recover.
作戦だとかプライドだとか
He'll do better without annoying
restraints, like strategies or pride.
そういうわずらわしい呪縛がない方がいいんだ
なるほど
I see.
I know what you mean.
そういう意味か
根底にあるもともともっていたものが目を覚ます
Something inside him
has to be awakened.
それだけでいいんだ
That's all he needs in a game
of tag on a mountain pass.
峠の追いかけっこなんて
Remember the basics.
原点に帰る
A battle tends to be settled
by something very simple.
ものすごくシンプルなもので勝負は決まるんだ
申しわけありません
I'm very sorry.
あんたがあやまることはない
You don't have to apologize.
The car is in great condition.
クルマはいい状態なんだ
オレの感触ではかなりいいタイムが出ているはずだ
My instinct tells me that
I had a pretty good time.
Am I wrong ?
ちがうか
おっしゃるとおりですな
You're exactly right.
第4区間では今もでの区間レコードを2秒ほど更新しています
You beat your own
section 4 record by 2 seconds.
だろ
See ?
I had good feedback.
手応えはあったんだ
It's not like I lost.
負けたわけじゃない
少してまどっているだけだ
I'm struggling a little,
but I'll recover from here.
ここからたてなおす
I've got to pull myself together.
この気持ちを なんとかたてなおす
行けるか 啓介
Ready to go, Keisuke ?
いつでもいいぜ
Anytime. I'll throw everything
I've got into this second run.
この2本目で全部はき出す
3本目があるなら 100%オレの負けだ
If this drags on into a
third run, I'll definitely lose.
悲壮感たっぷりなコメントのわりには 楽しそうだよな
You look like you're enjoying this, despite your desperate comment.
楽しいよ
I'm enjoying this from
the bottom of my heart.
体のシンからワクワクする
プロジェクトDが始まってから 一番今がうれしいかも
This could be my happiest
moment since Project D began.
Let's begin !
BGM为THE TOP 街机头文字D7AAX神曲
始めるぞォ
スタート5秒前
Five seconds till start !
4 3 2 1 ゴー
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Go !
3本目はない
There won't be a third run.
If there is, you'll lose.
あれば負ける
だけど よくここまで来たな 啓介
In any case, I'm proud of
what you've achieved, Keisuke.
手に汗にぎるとはこのことだよォ
This is breathtaking, isn't it ?
どこからみても情勢は不利だったのに
He was at a disadvantage in every aspect.
高橋啓介って昔からすごい走り屋だと思ってたけど
Takahashi Keisuke was an incredible street racer even back then...
オレ達の想像以上にすごくなってんだなァ
...but he turned out to be even
better than we imagined.
そっすよ だから言ったじゃないですか
Right.
Like I said, Project D's double
aces won't lose no matter what.
プロジェクトDのダブルエースは負けないって
だけとよ ターボってやっぱ
But turbo-charged cars tend to lose
power over time because of heat soak.
長い時間走ってると熱ダレしてパワーが落ちたりするから
勝負が長くなるのはFDにとって不利なんじゃないのかなァ
A longer race will negatively affect the FD.
それは高橋啓介が一番わかってるさ
Takahashi Keisuke should know
that better than anyone else.
どこかわかんないけど
I don't know where, but he'll make a spurt in the second half of the race.
後半てものすごいスパートをかけてくるぞ
すねぇ
I agree.
来た
Here they come !
しびれるなァ
I'm going to get a kick out of Takahashi Keisuke's cannonball dash which has beaten a number of tough challengers.
ここまで数多くの猛者達をねじふせてきた高橋啓介の弾丸スプリントが
この最高のステージでいよいよ炸裂するのかァ
It's going to be epic in this final stage.
I can't imagine what's gonna happen, or how the race will turn out.
どんな結果になるのか
何が起こるのか想像もつかない
何たって今走ってる二人は 速いってことに命をかけてるドライバーだからな
After all, both drivers are putting
their lives on the line to drive so fast.
あからさまに流していやがる 限界近くまで攻めていない
He's making it obvious that he's just cruising. He's not pushing it to the limit.
それでも速い スピードに乗っている
Even so, he's still fast, and
maintaining a high-speed pace.
うまいな これほどの芸当ができる男だったか
Nice execution.
I didn't expect him to be
able to pull off such a move.
こうして後ろについて 初めてわかることだな
I didn't realize he was so
skillful until I drove behind him.
それにしても なんとまあ気持ちよさそうに走るクルマだ
That aside, his car seems so fun to drive.
ショッキングなくらいだぜ こんな領域で バトルする奴がいたかな
It's quite shocking to see a driver who can compete at this high of a level.
オレのNSXも 外から見ていてあんなふうに見える時があっただろうか
Has my NSX ever looked
like that from the outside ?
ひきこまれる
I'm being sucked in...
この心地良いリズムにひきこまれてしまう
I'm being sucked in
by this pleasant rhythm...
シンクロしていく
...and getting synchronized.
それにしても解せませんね
I just don't get it.
ショップ対抗のタイムアタックでも FD3Sはたくさんいた
There are many FD3S's at time-attack events between tuning shops.
I've seen many time-attack specialty
FDs that looked like race cars.
タイムアタック仕様のレーシングカーみたいなFDも 何台も見てきた
あのクルマの欠点も長所もほぼわかっているつもりですがね
I thought I was well aware of that particular FD's strengths and weaknesses.
そのうえで勝ててるNSXに仕上げた自信はあります
I was confident that we'd
built a victory-worthy NSX.
オレには納得できませんよ 社長はどう思いますか
I don't understand this.
What do you think, Mr. Kubo ?
勝負ごとに絶対はないっちゅうことや
You can never be certain about
the outcome of a competition.
確かにデータの収集ではいっぱいくわされたが
We were outsmarted in data collection, but it's still within our expectations.
ギリギリ想定の範囲内とはいえる
万が一を考えて データにはゲタをはかせてシミュレーションをしているんや
We ran our simulation with a reasonable margin, just in case. We're not stupid.
わしらもバカじゃない
Maybe not by 15 seconds, but our
car still has an absolute advantage.
15秒とはいかんまでも
クルマには絶対にアドバンテージは残っている
やはりサーキットではありえないことが峠では起こる
After all, unlike circuits, unexpected things happen on mountain passes.
ここまでは相手のドライバーが ものすごくいい仕事をしているっちゅうことや
So far, our opponent is doing an excellent job.
まだ負けん
We haven't lost yet.
次はうちの大将がやり返す番や
This time, our leader will
turn the situation around.
この2本目さえしのげば 負ける材料はない
If he can manage this second run, there'll be no reason for us to lose.
圧倒的優位は動かんで
Nothing can shake our absolute advantage.
この心地良さもどこかで終わる
This pleasant feeling will
eventually come to an end.
戦闘モードにきりかわる瞬間がいずれ来る
There'll be a moment when
it will switch to combat mode.
オレが1本目にしたことと同じように
He'll make a full-throttle dash
like I did in the first run.
容赦ない全開スパートをかけてくる
それにオレとNSXがもちこたえられなければ その瞬間にこのバトルは終わる
If my NSX and I can't keep up
with it, this battle will be over.
どこだ どこで来る
Where...? Where are you
going to make your move ?
Fujiwara Takumi:
Takahashi Ryosuke:
Takahashi Keisuke:
Hojo Gou:
Kubo:
Miki Shinichiro
Koyasu Takehito
Seki Tomokazu
Kiuchi Hidenobu
Kase Yasuyuki
日の暮れに 変わらない景色
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Iketani Koichiro:
Kenji:
Matsumoto:
Fumihiro:
Inui Shinji:
Hojo Rin:
Ikeda Ryuji:
Omiya Satoshi:
Kogashiwa Kai:
Kobayakawa:
Minagawa Hideo:
Man:
Iwata Mitsuo
Yao Kazuki
Takagi Wataru
Nishi Rintaro
Hosoi Hajime
Abe Atsushi
Nakamura Yuichi
Nakai Kazuya
Touchi Hiroki
Canna Nobutoshi
Hamada Kenji
Konishi Katsuyuki
Takahashi Ryokichi
振り返る 辿ってきた道
Looking back at the path I've taken.
切なさも 喜びも 消えない痛みも
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains...
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
数えてたら限がないねと独り歩く
A
Central Anime
Production
Translation:
Hiro-kun
Timing:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Lillian-Hime
Barbara
Todd Perkins
Brain
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Nomake
Countless number of memorable scenes.
数え切れないほどの残像 ギャンブル生き抜いてきた残党
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
時に戦い 時に解りあい きれい事ばかりじゃなかった真実
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself...
背負ったまま新たな一歩
...as I take a new step.
あかね雲が街を染める この行く先をそっと問いかけて見る
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
空はなにもいわず だけど私にこの道を照らしている
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
透き通る景色を感じて
Feel the translucent scenery.
旋律を夕陽が奏で
The setting sun plays a melody.
透き通る景色を感じて
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.
旋律を夕陽が奏で